Well, I don't know if I'm ever going
back to America. When I heard about a
women's own business of handmade goods
in Colombia, I had to go. Everything in
here is handmade by women only. Coconut
purses, handmade linen clothing. I can
imagine Alex in this. Woof. And the
little ladies here are so friendly. Oh,
como estas? Bien, bien. I'm going to
bless these women today. I'm going to
drop some big money here. I got to get
this for Alex, this for Charlie, and
grab this for my little boy Mikey, this
for my daughter Lilly, this for little
Lilly, too. She turns five next month.
This for Colby so he can have a horse
hat, too. Undoubtedly. This one, this
one? That one. That That is the winner
right there. For 20 bucks, that one's
going to Alex. It looks like it's made
out of woven bamboo or some type of
plant. $37. That one's going home, too.
Final haul, handmade bikini top. I got a
wool bag, this cool brass necklace, a
shirt, a pair of pants, a full dress, a
custom hat, another dress, a neck romper
of some sort, another dress, this badass
bag, and this bag for $287
USD. This is just fantabulous. I don't
know if I'm ever going back to America.
Supporting local and supporting women
all at the same time. Viva Colombia.